- Dad! - Rick!  	 1.0
"""I love being your new Morty."""  	 1.0
"""Inception"" made sense."  	 1.0
"""The Creepy Morty"". What is it your kind's always saying? ""Don't think about it."" Come on. There's someone important I want you to meet."  	 1.0
"""The increment in the internal energy of a system is equal to the increment of heat supplied to the system."" Wow! I'm so smart!"  	 1.0
"""This is a great adventure."""  	 1.0
"Did he say ""three for three""?"  	 1.0
"I'm sorry. It's just like the end of ""Old Yeller."  	 1.0
"Rick says ""good"" and ""bad"" are artificial constructs."  	 1.0
"Some of my men are calling you ""Solen'ya"""  	 1.0
"The ""yes"" or ""no"" kind."  	 1.0
"Then what good was the ""yes""?"  	 1.0
"This article says the reason we weren't involved was... ""personality conflicts""."  	 1.0
"We're trying to incept me to get an ""A"" in math?"  	 1.0
"What is this place? And what's with ""Hunger Games"" Summer?"  	 1.0
"What part of ""blackout"" don't you understand? I thought you drank?"  	 1.0
"You talking about ""Inception""?"  	 1.0
...because this pickle doesn't care about your children. And I'm not gonna take their dreams. I'm gonna take their parents.  	 1.0
...Motherfucker!  	 1.0
?Mom and Dad?? Get your head out of your family's ass. The three of us are lost in a timeless oblivion. Your parents get to exist. They're probably living it up in some pointless grounded story about their shitty marriage.  	 1.0
1.77245385... Whoa!  	 1.0
A city of Grandpas?  	 1.0
A competent one.  	 1.0
A portal to the Blender Dimension?! That's the oldest trick in the book! I'm a Rick! I'm more Rick than any of you!!  	 1.0
A sequel.  	 1.0
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAHHHHHHHHHH!!!!!!!!!!  	 1.0
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHH!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!  	 1.0
AAAAAAAAAAAHHHHH!!!!!!!  	 1.0
AAAAAAAHHH!!!!!  	 1.0
AAAAAAAHHHH!!!!!!  	 1.0
Aaaaaah!  	 1.0
Aaaaah!  	 1.0
Aaaawwaaaaawaawa!  	 1.0
Aah!  Gun turret.  	 1.0
A-am I talking right now?  	 1.0
Absolutely not.  	 1.0
Absolutely.  	 1.0
After you.  	 1.0
Ah.  	 1.0
Ahh!  	 1.0
Ahhhhh yeahhhhh Ya gotta get schwifty  Ya gotta get schwifty in here It?s time to get schwifty  	 1.0
All aboard!  	 1.0
All of them.  	 1.0
All right!  	 1.0
Allahu  akbar! We're gonna take control of this plane! We're gonna 9/11 it unless Morty Smith gets better grades in math!  	 1.0
Almost... got it...  	 1.0
Alright. I'll-I'll land. I'll land. I'll land. I'll land the thing. I?ll land the thing. Big tough guy all of a sudden.  	 1.0
Am I me? I think so.  	 1.0
And away we go!  	 1.0
And how are you gonna do that?  	 1.0
And how is that?  	 1.0
And Jessica's gonna be Eve.  	 1.0
And she's saying what's important is that Grandpa lied to you to get out of coming here.  	 1.0
And sixteen quadrants. There's only enough time for a Jan-Michael Vincent to make it to a quadrant. He can't be in two quadrants at once.  	 1.0
And the chemical that makes his brain secrete goes into every Simple Rick?s Simple Wafer Cookie.  Come home to the impossible flavor of your own completion. Come home to Simple Rick?s.  	 1.0
And then Ethan played guitar and we learned the Seven Contemplations of the Head by singing them. It was really fun. Praise be the head!  	 1.0
And you did it so you could clean the house after a party?  	 1.0
And?  	 1.0
Anything. Anything for my precious Morty.  	 1.0
Are those cats?  	 1.0
Are we gonna go back?  	 1.0
Are you all right?  	 1.0
Are you going to set all their nukes to target each other?  	 1.0
Are you gonna build them?  	 1.0
Are you kidding me?! Come on!  	 1.0
Are you okay?  	 1.0
Are you sure there's not just a picnic nearby.  	 1.0
Aww.  	 1.0
BACK OFF I'M TRYING TO BE WITH MY MAN!  	 1.0
Bad person. Bad.  	 1.0
Barely.  	 1.0
B-b-but we don?t have a song!  	 1.0
Because I wish that would change. I wish anything about this life would change.  	 1.0
Because my epidermis is laced with a nanofiber defense mesh.  	 1.0
Because Ricks hate themselves the most. And our Rick is the most himself.  	 1.0
Because we're both rational adults that don't want anything bad to happen. And because I have a human shield.  	 1.0
Because you love her!  	 1.0
Begin phase two.  	 1.0
Beth!  	 1.0
Birdperson?  	 1.0
BOO! NOT COOL!  	 1.0
Boo-nah?  	 1.0
Bootleg portal fluid.  	 1.0
Boo-yah!  	 1.0
But I thought there were infinite timelines.  	 1.0
But I-it's been like a whole year!  	 1.0
But that's the opposite of what-  	 1.0
But the top deer surgeon...  	 1.0
But you guys have always had a... an unspoken bond.  	 1.0
But you're betting our lives on it.  	 1.0
But.. she was trying to kill us!  	 1.0
But... I violated at least a dozen departmental codes!  	 1.0
But?  	 1.0
By changing you from a pickle to a human.  	 1.0
CALL ME A SIDEKICK ONE MORE TIME!?CALL ME A SIDEKICK!!  	 1.0
Call off the nuclear strike! This is the President. Stop the nuclear missile launch!  	 1.0
Can I show these to you?  	 1.0
Can the Pope?s dick fit through a donut?  	 1.0
Can't argue with that.  	 1.0
Can't we just portal home?  	 1.0
Can't you just turn yourself back into a human?  	 1.0
Chris!  	 1.0
Close. It's gonna make your kidneys shut down.  	 1.0
Cold Stone Creamery is the best. What should we do with our remaining twenty dollars?  	 1.0
Come get this delicious brine.  	 1.0
Come on. That's it.  	 1.0
Congrats! You did it-- it!  	 1.0
Dad I would like you to tell me what's in the syringe.  	 1.0
Dad?  	 1.0
Damn it!  	 1.0
Damn! She double-crossed Snuzzles!  	 1.0
Damn. You didn?t tell me you fuck around with portals and shit.  	 1.0
Dear God.  	 1.0
Destroying the  galactic government.  	 1.0
Did he just say ?musical reality show??  	 1.0
Did he say he never forgets a kid?  	 1.0
Did we miss graduation? Where are the new Ricks?  	 1.0
DIIIIEEEE!!!!  	 1.0
Dinner sounds nice.  	 1.0
DISQUALIFIED!  	 2.0
DISQUALIFIED! DISQUALIFIED!  	 1.0
Do not call me that!  	 1.0
Do not threaten her!  	 1.0
Do the cabbage patch. Do?do?do the dance.  	 1.0
Do you know what I want you to do with them?  	 1.0
Do you realize how many codes you just violated?  	 1.0
Do you really not see what's happening here?  	 1.0
Does Grandpa turn himself into a pickle a lot?  	 1.0
Don't think about it!  	 1.0
Don't worry about Jerry. He's gonna be fine.You hear me Jerry? You're gonna be fine!  	 1.0
Doomnomitron was hiding here! He's a shapeshifter! Destroying Dorian 5 was the only way to kill him!  	 1.0
Duh!  	 1.0
Eh.  	 1.0
Every day.  	 1.0
Exactly!  	 1.0
Excuse me?  	 1.0
Eye-holes! Get them today! IKEA.  	 1.0
Farty!  	 1.0
Fifteen years.  	 1.0
Fifth and ? That?s Mortytown.  	 1.0
Fine I'll just do it myself.  	 1.0
Five plus five.  	 1.0
Five?  	 1.0
Flip the pickle over.  	 1.0
For everybody.  	 2.0
Frank Palicky was frozen to death today!  	 1.0
Fuck you.  	 1.0
Geez. I didn?t know there were still Ricks and Mortys living on the Citadel. I wonder what their day-to-day lives are like.  	 1.0
Geez...  	 1.0
Get it yourself.  	 1.0
Get that parkour. Get that parkour!  	 1.0
Get this man and his grandson on a Blackhawk to Area 51.  	 1.0
GET YOUR HANDS OFF OF HIM!  	 1.0
Get? schwifty? What the hell is that?  	 1.0
Give me one good reason why I shouldn't crush your windpipe!  	 1.0
Go to the bathroom.  	 1.0
Go to the car and grab a MediPack. Lemme worry about this.  	 1.0
God... fuckin' dammit!  Fine! But don't say I didn't warn you.  	 1.0
Goddammit!  	 1.0
Good question. I suppose the answer is  	 1.0
Gosh. We moved around so much it?s hard to remember. I see every Rick as my Rick.  	 1.0
Got it.  	 1.0
Got some of that mermaid puss!  	 1.0
Grandpa Rick wouldn't put up with this!  	 1.0
Grandpa Rick!  	 1.0
Great. We'll see you later.  	 1.0
Greater good?!  	 1.0
Guess his math was off. Search the place.  	 1.0
Guess who dismantled the government?  	 1.0
Guys!  I've figured it out.  	 1.0
Ha!  	 1.0
Ha-ha!  	 1.0
Hands in the air!  	 1.0
Happy hour.  	 1.0
He got captured by the Federation and we were going to rescue him.  	 1.0
He gotta be stopped...  He-he cou-couldn't be allowed to win.  	 1.0
He realized long ago that the greatest thing he?d ever create was his daughter.  	 1.0
He turned himself into a pickle.  	 1.0
He... won?  	 1.0
Headism is a hit. We?re taking it worldwide and would like Jerry to be our church?s ?Head? of Advertising.  	 1.0
Headward free now to rise!  	 1.0
HEEEEELLLLPPPP!!!!!  	 1.0
Hello? Is anybody here?  Mr. President!  	 1.0
He's in prison.  	 1.0
He's just a pickle!  	 1.0
He's not the only one.  	 1.0
He's right. This is far from over.  	 1.0
Hey there. How you doing? Great to meet you.  	 1.0
Hey!  Did you end up getting a new job?  	 1.0
Hey! Look at the heads! Looks like the heads are gettin? angry!  	 1.0
Hey.  	 1.0
Hmm...  	 1.0
Hmm... you'd have to be pretty petty. But you'd still be the woman I married.  	 1.0
Hmm?  	 1.0
Hold your fire! Hold your fire! I'm Morty C-137.  	 1.0
Holy CRAP!  	 1.0
Holy crap!  	 1.0
Holy crap! This is insane!  	 1.0
Holy crap. He's right.  	 1.0
Holy crap... Slick's wish came true.  	 1.0
Holy shit! What happened?  	 1.0
Holy shit.  I don?t believe it! I-I can?t believe it!  	 1.0
Holy shit.  	 1.0
Holy shit. You're jealous.  	 1.0
How did this happen?  	 1.0
How do you know about that?  	 1.0
How is praying going to help?  	 1.0
How is this a fair trial? O-Our lawyer is a Morty.  	 1.0
How is this even family therapy if Dad's not invited and Grandpa won't come?  	 1.0
How long exactly do we have to wear these things? They're really embarassing.  	 1.0
Huh! You think you can control me with a haircut?  	 1.0
Huh... no accounting for taste. I'm gonna go get a drink.  	 1.0
Huh?  	 1.0
Huh? What are you -- What are you doing?  	 1.0
Humans understand snuffles now? That is awesome!  	 1.0
Hundreds of billions.  	 1.0
I always hated that song!  	 1.0
I AM a baby! I?m a baby NOW!  	 1.0
I am afraid that my kids will get expelled.  	 1.0
I am mad that I can't huff enamel without people assuming it's because my family sucks. I hope to be seen one day as someone that just likes getting high.  	 1.0
I am Phoenixperson.  	 1.0
I am sad that I peed. I'm sad that I peed in class instead of a toilet.  	 1.0
I believe I can access the history of Rick?s gun and help you get back to him.  	 1.0
I bet it leads to a place where a bunch of fri-- flies everywhere!  	 1.0
I better tend to Jerry before he changes his mind and doesn't move out. I will leave you two to your adventures.  	 1.0
I cannot argue that.  	 1.0
I can't believe how mean snuffles got just because he's smart.  	 1.0
I could--It could be Morty.  	 1.0
I could've just used a ghost train.  	 1.0
I didn't!  	 1.0
I didn't. I did.  	 1.0
I do?  	 1.0
I don?t know what to say. Summer is doing really well here.  	 1.0
I don?t see a divide between Ricks and Mortys.  	 1.0
I done been notifying you. Have you not been getting the messages I've been leaving with Morty's grandfather?  	 1.0
I don't care about Jessica! Y-Yyyyyyyyyyou?  	 1.0
I don't know yet. I'll make it up as I go. That's what Grandpa Rick does. That's what heroes do.  	 1.0
I don't know. I think like one sixty-fourth of my collars didn't work. It's hard to keep straight now that I have sixty-three other memories of everything.  	 1.0
I don't know. It's Indian giving.  	 1.0
I don't think so. See you soon.  	 1.0
I don't want to talk about it!  	 1.0
I feel pretty confident about tonight?s debate.  	 1.0
I guess I shoulda had more faith.  	 1.0
I guess I wish I had something cooler than this dumbass surfer necklace.  	 1.0
I guess that's the end of that.  	 1.0
I hate you!  	 1.0
I have changed. I am ready to rejoin my brethren on Alphabetrium.  	 1.0
I have no stake in this.  	 1.0
I hit a deer! W-we have to tell the cops you were driving.  	 1.0
I hope they see me as their Morty.  	 1.0
I know.  That?s why you?re fired.  	 1.0
I love this man!  	 1.0
I love you guys. You gave me life. And it?s the will of the many heads that all children honor their parents.  	 1.0
I mean it's been shot. With a gun.  	 1.0
I need five minutes.  	 1.0
I never said I was angry at you.  	 1.0
I say we make our last day count. I say? we go to the Wishing Portal.  	 1.0
I say?  Let?s do it!  	 1.0
I see there's a new episode of that singing show tonight. Who do you guys think is gonna be the best singer?  	 1.0
I see-WAIT! What?  	 1.0
I sense his life force is fading.  	 1.0
I sense the presence of a greater evil.  	 1.0
I sense this means we are not drying.  	 1.0
I sense... insecurity.  	 1.0
I should call Bob Saget. Is that still a thing?  	 1.0
I think I'm certain we're F'd in the A.  	 1.0
I think planet Earth has just been transported.  	 1.0
I told the both of you school is stupid. It's not how you learn things. Morty's a gifted child. He has a special mind. That's why he's my little helper. He's like me. He's gonna be doing great science stuff later in his life. He's too smart for school. He needs to keep hanging out and helping me.  	 1.0
I told you not to invite this mummified motherfucker back!  	 1.0
I told you past the dinosaurs.  	 1.0
I wanted to let you all know that Jerry is doing just fine.  	 1.0
I was right. He turned himself in on purpose. It was all part of his plan!  	 1.0
I was told there was a grandpa that might be joining us?  	 1.0
I wish he had the ability to check is attitude.  	 1.0
I wouldn't be much of a pickle if I could.  	 1.0
I... think the personality conflict might have been... you.  	 1.0
I?m going to go find Mom and Dad.  	 1.0
I?m going to start dinner!  	 1.0
I?m sorry?  	 1.0
I?m sure that has? that has nothing to do with this.  	 1.0
I?m the only one that speaks to the heads!  	 1.0
I?ve seen enough. These guys are one-hit wonders.  	 1.0
If we hurry we can set up camp in a sewer tunnel or something before the dogs completely take over.  	 1.0
If you could get out that whole time why didn't you?  	 1.0
If you lay those deaths at my doorstep one more time...  	 1.0
I-I thought I saw a fly.  	 1.0
I-I totally get it. I-I'm so sorry.  	 1.0
I-I-I don't know what you mean by that. Can can can you be a little bit more specific?  	 1.0
I-I-I... I'm not a superhero.  	 1.0
I-I'm just trying to figure out why you would do this. Why anyone would do this.  	 1.0
I-It's just something Rick starts talking about whenever he's blackout drunk.  	 1.0
I'll cover that bet. I get it.  	 1.0
I'll take two.  	 1.0
I'm a full season behind.  	 1.0
I'm gonna pee my pants.  	 1.0
I'm gonna pee-hee-hee.  	 1.0
I'm looking at her. Thanks for F.D.'ing me up like that.  	 1.0
I'm not letting you let my sister die! Drop the gun!  	 1.0
I'm not the one that didn't want you back. Alan was!  	 1.0
I'm okay... I'm okay... I'm...  Ohh...  	 1.0
In my butt?  	 2.0
Is he going to die?  	 1.0
Is it important that we know who Jan-Michael Vincent is in order to get this?  	 1.0
Is that--  	 1.0
Is that sarcasm?!  I don't want you slipping away then this is over! All of these deaths are on your hands!  	 1.0
Is that something we should be concerned about?  	 1.0
Is the helicopter here?  	 1.0
Is this what I think it is?  	 1.0
Isn't there a kitten somewhere that needs a manicure?  	 1.0
It doesn?t matter.  Nothing?s wrong with putting your faith in a Morty. You just gotta pick the right one.  	 1.0
It is random debris. I found it in my carpet. I don?t know what humans eat.  	 1.0
It was a bit. All of the descriptors apply to all of you. Drunk Rick's point is that none of you are very special or different.  That's always his point.  	 1.0
It was?  	 1.0
It's a monster!  	 2.0
It's a trap! Abort! I'm still in his Shoney's! Repeat -- we never left his Shoney's!  	 1.0
It's a trap! Abort! We never left his --   No!  	 1.0
It's better than making your problems other people's problems.  	 1.0
It's not my fault we froze time on a humid day!  	 1.0
It's personal.  	 1.0
It's still alive.  	 1.0
It's the Citadel of Ricks. All the different Ricks from all the different realities got together to hide here from the government.  	 1.0
It's the galaxy's faith in the Vindicators that keeps the galaxy secure!  	 1.0
It's the middle of the night. What are you talking about?  	 1.0
It's Worldender! What happened to him?  	 1.0
I've heard a lot about you today. Your family is crazy about you. Your daughter holds you in very high regard. You're a lucky fella.  	 1.0
I've replaced them both as the de facto patriarch of your family and your universe. Your mom wouldn't have accepted me if I came home -  	 1.0
Jaguar couldn't make it.  	 1.0
Jaguar was an animal. You're an intelligent pickle. We can do business.  	 1.0
Jaguar!  	 1.0
Jaguar's daughter is dead.  	 1.0
Jan-Michael Vincent's are used up.  	 1.0
Je-Jessica. Jessica.  	 1.0
Jerry!  	 1.0
Jerry?  	 2.0
Jerry's going to spend some time divorced.  	 1.0
Jessica.  	 3.0
Jessica? From my math class?  	 1.0
Jesus!  	 1.0
Jesus...  	 1.0
Just launch the missiles!  	 1.0
Just somethin? they do to make you feel bad.  	 1.0
Just stay away from the coffee machine.  	 1.0
Leaving a partial length of severed urethra to be threaded through-  	 1.0
Lemme turn over a few rocks.  	 1.0
LET ME GO!!! I LOVE YOU MORTY!  	 1.0
Let's do an experiment here. I get the impression this family values science. So raise your hand if you feel certain you know what was in the syringe.  	 1.0
Let's see if he needs help.  	 1.0
Like we?re not already under enough pressure!  	 1.0
line  	 1.0
Listen! The storm is stopping!  	 1.0
Look at this family go. You guys are pros. What do you guys think about doing this once a week?  	 1.0
Looks like scary Terry's having a nightmare.  	 1.0
Looks like some sort of legally safe knock-off of an '80s horror character with miniature swords for fingers instead of knives.  	 1.0
Make it bounce.  	 1.0
Man. Glad I?m not one of them!  	 1.0
Maybe I just want you to care if I run away yelling!  	 1.0
Maybe... Maybe he went somewhere nice.  	 1.0
McNuggets?  	 1.0
Me too.  	 1.0
Me too. How long have you all been eating poop?  	 1.0
Me!  	 2.0
Me. I used to wear blue pants.  	 1.0
Me? What about you? Would you get more excited to see me fail? You want Grampa all to yourself!  	 1.0
Mm-hmm.  	 1.0
Morty and I are going to look into it. You guys hold tight.  	 1.0
Morty let's-let's see what else is on.  	 1.0
Morty!  	 4.0
Morty! What are you doing to me?!  	 1.0
Morty! You gotta come on. Jus'... you gotta come with me.  	 1.0
Morty.  	 2.0
Morty...  	 1.0
Morty?  	 2.0
Mortys are human!  	 1.0
Mr. Bulldops?  	 1.0
Mrs. Pancakes! AAAAAAAAHHHH!!!!!  	 1.0
My balls.  	 1.0
My goodness.  	 1.0
My kids pee their desks and suck on unbaked vases.  	 1.0
My name is Rick Sanchez. This here?s my grandson Morty.  	 1.0
Never said that!  	 1.0
Nice shot.  	 1.0
No doubt. Who do we make the check out to?  	 1.0
No graduation. No new Ricks. The school's curriculum is changing.  	 1.0
No idea what you're talking about.  	 1.0
No it doesn't. It hurts.  	 1.0
No longer will the insects have domain over surface world!  	 1.0
No way.  	 1.0
No! Stop that! You?re not allowed to interpret the will of the heads!  	 1.0
No! Why?! Why would you do that?! W-W-What is the matter with you people?!  	 1.0
No.  	 1.0
Noo.  	 1.0
Nooooo!  	 1.0
Nooooooo!  	 1.0
NOOOOOOOO!!!!  	 1.0
Nope.  	 1.0
Not all of us.  	 1.0
Not anymore.  	 1.0
Not my fault this is happening.  	 1.0
Not until I finish what I started. And that is how you get level-nine access without a password.  	 1.0
Nothing!  	 1.0
Nothing?! We exterminated a planet!  	 1.0
Now bring me my slippers.  	 1.0
Nuh uh!  	 1.0
Oh God! We?re up?!?!  	 1.0
Oh God...  	 1.0
Oh man... I don't feel good.  	 1.0
Oh my God! C-c-can you fly a Blackhawk?  	 1.0
Oh shit.  	 1.0
Oh!  	 1.0
Oh! Oh!  	 1.0
Oh.  	 1.0
Ohh! Oh! Gross! Gross!  	 1.0
Ohh...  	 1.0
Ohhh my GOOOOODDDD!!!  	 1.0
Ohhhh yeahhhh!  	 2.0
Ohhhh!  	 1.0
Ohhhhh!  	 1.0
Ohhhhhh!  	 1.0
Ok?  	 1.0
Okay.  	 1.0
O-kayyy...  	 1.0
Oldest Rick trick in the book.  	 1.0
One last stop.  	 1.0
One million times better!  	 1.0
Oof! Didn't see that comin'.  	 1.0
Ooh!  	 1.0
Ooh! Ohh! Ooh! Hnngh! Hoo! Ooh! Ohh! Aaaaagh! Oooooh!  	 1.0
Ooohhh!  	 1.0
Ooooooaaahhh!  	 1.0
Ooooooohhhhh! Holy crap!  	 1.0
Ooooyayawawa!  	 1.0
Ooowwwwowowwaawaa!  	 1.0
Or maybe you were out all night again with Grandpa Rick.  	 1.0
Or the Series 9000 is going to turn it into mush.  	 1.0
Or...  	 1.0
Or?  	 1.0
Our time is fractured. You two somehow created a feedback loop of uncertainty that's split our reality into two equally possible impossiblities. W-we're exactly like a man capable of sustaining a platonic friendship with an attractive female co-worker. We're entirely hypothetical.  	 1.0
Our time is gonna be unstable? What does that even mean?  	 1.0
Outside?  	 1.0
Ow! Ow! You're tugging me too hard!  	 1.0
Oww!  	 1.0
Phew...  	 1.0
Pickle Riiick!  	 1.0
Please be kind to us for we are but tiny things with entire bodies stuck to your ground.  	 1.0
Please don't leave me again.  	 1.0
Relaxed enough?  	 1.0
Rename them?  	 1.0
Require different levels of skill to keep alive?  	 1.0
Rick what the hell are you doing?  	 1.0
Rick!  	 2.0
RICK!  	 1.0
Rick. And I'm--  	 1.0
Rick?  	 2.0
Rick? W-where are you?  	 1.0
Right.  	 1.0
Right...  	 1.0
Right?  	 1.0
Roll over.  	 1.0
R-Rick?  	 1.0
Same old story. Mortys killing Mortys.  	 1.0
Same old story. Ricks killing Mortys.  	 1.0
Sanchez! Are you a musician?  	 1.0
Saving our lives. After he takes me out he's gonna be coming for you!  	 1.0
Say it with me!  	 1.0
Scalpel.  	 1.0
Scaring you?  	 1.0
Screw this. I'm not playing his game. I'm gonna find us a way out of here.  	 1.0
Sex is sacred!  	 1.0
She normally works on horses.  	 1.0
She?s not getting pregnant or doing drugs or missing curfew?  	 1.0
She's gonna be alone with that guy all night.  	 1.0
Shit.  	 1.0
Shoney's.  	 1.0
SHOW ME WHAT YOU GOT.  	 1.0
Shut up!  Oh crap are you kidding me? Two dots? This never needs to be more than one dot. The two of you made us uncertain!  	 1.0
Shut up.  	 1.0
Silence! I'm going to enjoy this...  	 1.0
SLI-I-I-I-I-I-I-ICK!!!!  	 1.0
Smith family?  	 1.0
Snuffles fix. Make better.  	 1.0
Snuffles want to be understood. Snuffles need to be understood.  	 1.0
Snuffles.  	 1.0
So I wouldn't have to come here.  	 1.0
So report me. Nobody gives a fuck.  	 1.0
So...  	 1.0
So... hot. This is how I'm gonna die.  	 1.0
Someone special you remember? Is that your memory of her out there -- between where you were on 9/11 and your favorite sports blooper?  	 1.0
Someone wake up Sanchez.  	 1.0
Son of a steam engine! They're all dead!  	 1.0
Sorry I'm late. It was happy hour.  	 1.0
Sort of.  	 1.0
Sounds lonely.  	 1.0
S-smartest man in the universe.  	 1.0
Stand down. Everybody stand down! I?m the leader of these people and I?m unarmed. There?s no need for any more snake-makery.  	 1.0
Stay back! This watch turns people into snakes!  	 1.0
Stop saying his name! He abandoned us.  	 1.0
Stop saying it like it?s a thing! You made it up!  	 1.0
STOP!  	 1.0
Summer.  	 1.0
Summer?  	 1.0
Sure thing! And I was kinda hoping that I could get a selfie with you?  	 1.0
Sure! Let?s go to the Ascension. Wh-wh-what is it?  	 1.0
Sweetheart?  	 1.0
Szechuan?  	 1.0
Taco time!  I hope it pleases you as the head desires.  	 1.0
Take a shit on the floor Time to get schwifty in here  	 1.0
Take off your pants and your panties Shit on the floor Time to get schwifty in here I?m Mr. Bulldops  	 1.0
Takes one to know one.  	 1.0
Tell me.  	 1.0
Tell them we were robbed.  	 1.0
Temporarily. By order of the school.  	 1.0
Thank you.  	 1.0
Thanks to Cold Stone Creamery.  	 1.0
That is a... really specific guess.  	 1.0
That son of a bitch is gonna kill me!  	 1.0
That was amazing!  	 1.0
That?s a myth.  	 1.0
That?s it!  	 1.0
That?s my dream! That?s my dream.  	 1.0
That?s not our business as long as Summer is thriving!  	 1.0
That'd be a lucky break for you.  	 1.0
That's a three-pointer!  	 4.0
That's enough Bradley. We don't want you injuring your ball-throwing arm.  	 1.0
That's enough!  	 1.0
That's Jan-Michaels.  	 1.0
That's my sister. This used to be my home.  	 1.0
The Citadel?s problem is the Ricks and Mortys feeding on the Citadel?s debt.  	 1.0
The day I invented the portal gun is the day I lost her.  	 1.0
The election?s got these yellow shirts more riled up than a Picture Day Jessica.  	 1.0
The galactic government collapsed.  	 1.0
The glarp zone is for flarping and unglarping only.  	 2.0
The head has left and sent its children!  	 1.0
The heads are displeased!  	 1.0
The heads disqualified Vagina! Get him!  	 1.0
The heads love this! They love it when we DON?T kill the Smith family!  	 1.0
The kind that wasn't designed to attack or hurt you in any way.  	 1.0
The little girl!  	 1.0
The mega trees?  	 1.0
The name's not buddy. It's Goldenfold. Nice to wheat you!  	 1.0
The point is he thought I was going to.  	 1.0
The trick to cereal is keeping 70% of it above the milk.  	 1.0
The two of us?!  I hope you're proud of yourself!  	 1.0
The world?  	 1.0
Then why aren't we killing them?!  	 1.0
Then why did you bring us here?  	 1.0
Then you should use your left hand to eat more vegetables.  	 1.0
There is no helicopter and there is no Cervine Institute.  	 1.0
There?s one every season. Moving on to planet Arbolez Meterosos. Arbolian Meterososians. SHOW US WHAT YOU GOT.  	 1.0
There's nothing I won't do to see her again.  	 1.0
They didn't  let me out.  	 1.0
They had a little accident. They won't be causing any trouble anymore.  	 1.0
They tried to murder him first.  	 1.0
This is Bluebird. Code tango-niner-alpha. Abort launch. Abort! Hello?  He?s blocked me out.  	 1.0
This is just like a Morty baby!  	 1.0
This is Rum Raisin!  	 1.0
This is what I'm talking about. This is a dog.  	 1.0
This is why I choose to get C's.  	 1.0
This late?  	 1.0
Time prison?  	 1.0
Titty-Bean?  	 1.0
To the day it all began and ended. The moment that changed everything.  	 1.0
To what?  	 1.0
T-t-that's absolutely crazy!  	 1.0
Ugghh  	 1.0
Ugh.  	 1.0
Uh oh.  	 1.0
Uhhh ...  	 1.0
Uh-huh.  	 1.0
Uh-oh! Spoilers!  	 1.0
Uh-oh.  	 1.0
Um...  	 1.0
Ummm  	 1.0
Understood.  	 1.0
Unit 7 responding.  	 1.0
Ututututut! You'd better keep back! Man this will turn your ass into a third trimester fetus from 30 yards.  	 1.0
Uuuh.  	 1.0
WANNA SEE HOW I PAINT A WALL?!  	 1.0
Want kinda question is that?  	 1.0
Was it?  	 1.0
We ?isn't?  	 1.0
We all do.  	 1.0
We are not them! We are not them.  	 1.0
We captured that moment and run it on a loop through Simple Rick?s mind.  	 1.0
We did it...  	 1.0
We had a little incident. A student was frozen to death.  And there's no evidence that a Latino student did it! Everyone wants to take this to a racial place. I won't let them.  	 1.0
We should go get him.  	 1.0
We should pack up and leave town now.  	 1.0
We... have never... eaten poop.  	 1.0
We?ll take our chances raising her without fancy new jobs outside of a potato-based religion.  And you know what? I?m sick of pretending that we?re together because of the kids in the first place! I married you because you?re the love of my life!  	 1.0
Weird breed.  	 1.0
Well don't different animals-  	 1.0
Well is there some way you can prove you're not a threat to yourself and others anymore?  	 1.0
Were either of you guys uncertain about anything just now?  	 1.0
We're moving you to a nursing home.  	 1.0
What -- What's this supposed to accomplish? We have infinite grandkids. You're trying to use Disney bucks at a Caesar's Palace here.  	 1.0
What are we here for again? Incepting? We're trying to incept-  	 1.0
What are you doing with that?!  	 1.0
What are you doing?  	 1.0
What are you talking about?  	 1.0
What are you talking about? This is a memory. Y-You can't alter details of a memory.  	 1.0
What are you talking about?!  	 2.0
What are you trying to say about Morty? That he's stupid or something?  	 1.0
What do you mean you're gonna help him.  	 1.0
What do you mean?  	 2.0
What does that mean?  	 1.0
What happened?  	 1.0
What if I told you there's a huge ticket up right behind you?  	 1.0
What is it?  	 1.0
What is that?!  	 1.0
What is the place?  	 1.0
What kind of God lets this happen?  	 1.0
What new-  what new machine?  	 1.0
What should we do Morty?  	 1.0
What the fuck?  	 1.0
What the fuck? You can turn into ice?  	 1.0
What the FUCK?!  	 1.0
What the hell happened?  	 1.0
What the hell is Is-ra-el?  	 1.0
What the hell is wrong with you two!? I?I m?I m?I mean you four!?  	 1.0
What the hell?  	 3.0
What the hell? Why would Mr. Goldenfold's dream version of Mrs.  	 1.0
What what are you guys doing with my stuff?  	 1.0
WHAT!?!  	 1.0
What?  	 6.0
What? English please?  	 1.0
What? Every hospital claims to have the best doctor in the galaxy. It's like those pizza places that claim to have the best pizza in the world. What- Do you think they have pizza contests? Have you ever been to a pizza contest?  	 1.0
What? For real?  	 1.0
What? How is that possible? Do people just die when I name them?  	 1.0
What? In English?  	 1.0
What? What kind of monster are you?  	 1.0
What? What the hell are you doing?  	 1.0
What? Why are you looking at me? You want to go outside? Outside?  	 1.0
What? Why didn't you notify us?  	 1.0
What? Why not?  	 1.0
WHAT?!  	 1.0
What?!  	 4.0
What?! A bomb?!  	 1.0
What?! Are you kidding me?! Ohhhhhh!  	 1.0
What?! What happened?  	 1.0
What?s that? Who?s that baby?  	 1.0
What?s this?  	 1.0
Whatever. How petty would I have to be to care less about an animal's life than my own ego?  	 1.0
What's happening Grampa?  	 1.0
What's up Morty?  	 1.0
What's wrong?  	 1.0
What's yours?  	 1.0
Wheat thins. Wheat thins.  	 1.0
When did it get so complicated?  	 1.0
When I--  	 1.0
When'd you make the leap to interdimensional travel?  	 1.0
Where am I?  	 1.0
Where are we going?  	 3.0
Where are you guys going?  	 1.0
Where is it?  	 1.0
Where the fuck is the lead wire?!  	 1.0
Where's the helicopter?  	 1.0
Whhhh-wha?  	 1.0
Who cares about the  thing you guys are talking about? The whole point of freezing time is to stop giving a fuck. Put a shirt on your dumb dad and let's get this dumb universe rolling. Let's do this thing.  	 1.0
Who cares how high they promote you? Everyone just gets paid in pills.  	 1.0
Who cares? Just hold me.  	 1.0
Who knows? But we can make it simple again.  	 1.0
Who the fuck is Noob-Noob?  	 1.0
Who would take a lobster to see Iron Man 3?  	 1.0
Who?  	 1.0
Whoa whoa wh-what the hell hell hell hell hell?  	 1.0
Whoa whoa!  	 1.0
Whoa!  	 1.0
Whoa! Look at you! You?re wearing the hat and everything!  	 1.0
Whoa! Look! It's that lady with all that shit on her face like Worf from Star Trek! That was getting coffee! How did she get there!  	 1.0
Whoa! Who in the fuck's toilet is this?  	 1.0
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa! Whoooooaaaa! Whoa! Whoa! Whoooooaaaa!  	 1.0
WHOA!!  	 1.0
Whooooa! Whoooooooa! Whoa! Whooooooooaaaaa!  	 1.0
Whoooooo!  	 1.0
Who's this now?  	 1.0
Why am I still here? I already confessed to everything.  	 1.0
Why are you acting like that's not you?!  	 1.0
Why are you doing this?  	 1.0
Why didn?t he turn into a snake?  	 1.0
Why didn't you want to come here?  	 1.0
Why does he have to go over there?  	 1.0
Why is there a crib in here?  	 1.0
Why not shoot through her?  	 1.0
Why not?  	 2.0
Why would you keep mutant bacteria in a pint of Cherry Garcia?  	 1.0
Willem Dafoe! Th-That's the guy I couldn't think of this morning.  	 1.0
Woahh!  	 1.0
Woohoo! Whoo! Whoo!  	 1.0
Worst-case scenario we're back to running.  	 1.0
Wow. Did you just come into the cafeteria through a portal?  	 1.0
Wow. This sauce is fucking amazing. You said it was promoting a movie?  	 1.0
Wow. Th-they're both great. Thank you!  	 1.0
Wow. Ugh.  	 1.0
W-We just missed you a lot.  	 1.0
W-what?  	 1.0
W-what're you doing?  	 1.0
W-w-w-what is it?  	 1.0
Yeah huh!  	 1.0
Yeah.  	 3.0
Yeah. That's the three lines of math that separates my life as a man from my life as an unfeeling ghost.  	 1.0
Yeah. Totally. Let's go.  	 1.0
Yeah?  	 1.0
Yes Beth.  	 1.0
Yes!  	 1.0
YES! Is that what you want to hear?!  	 1.0
Yes.  	 1.0
Yes. I only lost 400 ants. My queen is laying more.  I am back to one million ants.  	 1.0
Yes?  	 2.0
Yess.  	 1.0
You admire him for that.  	 1.0
You better stop with that.  	 1.0
You can run But you can't hide!  	 1.0
You didn't what?  	 1.0
You don?t have to be a dick.  	 1.0
You don?t pay me to have faith! And we?re the same age!  	 1.0
You don't know m-  	 1.0
You don't know me!  	 2.0
You got it.  	 1.0
You guys doin? a little chemistry homework with Grandpa?  	 1.0
You guys should really not be touching that stuff. It's beyond your reasoning.  	 1.0
You killed my gun!  	 1.0
You know what I named these? My little Morties.  	 1.0
You know what? Okay.  	 1.0
You lied! You lied about the charge! You were just being lazy! Get back! Sit down!  	 1.0
You make fun of me all the time and now Summer's doing it too!  	 1.0
You mean drunk?  	 1.0
You must be Rick.  	 1.0
You realize they sing no matter how much you tip.  	 1.0
You really think I'm that stupid?  	 1.0
You should be.  Running around in a yellow t-shirt like you're not one of us? Disgraceful.  	 1.0
You should know that isn't original.  	 1.0
You should know those men killed themselves.  	 1.0
You shut up you big... female asshole!  	 1.0
You shut up!  	 1.0
You stole a time freezing crystal from testical monsters?  	 1.0
You tried to kill yourself!  	 1.0
You two make quite a team.  	 1.0
You were always the romantic.  Which is why you can't leave either.  	 1.0
You were right?  Everything I learned in the academy was--  	 1.0
You will walk when it is time to walk.  	 1.0
You wish this was about sex! We loved each other! We had a child together.  	 1.0
You? would?  	 1.0
You?re going to be ok!  You will come back as babies!  	 1.0
You?re gonna wanna put them on that giant speaker system at your sonic testing facility at Area 51.  	 1.0
Your idiot dog!  	 1.0
Your kids think it might be anti-pickle serum.  	 1.0
Your mere presence in this building violates international law.  	 1.0
You're alive!  	 1.0
You're always picking on me and now you got someone to kiss your ass!  	 1.0
You're beyond our reasoning!  	 1.0
You're gonna deny it.  	 1.0
You're overreacting!  	 1.0
You're right!  	 1.0
You're the one that costs $200 an hour. You tell me.  	 1.0
